Max  你能帮我照看下那桌吗
Max. Can you watch my tables
我去趟洗手间
while I run to the restroom?
我看着那桌的女模特有一会儿了
I already am. I've been watching that model girl
30分钟了  她一直假装在吃东西呢
pretend she is eating for 30 minutes.
噢  她人很好
Oh. She is nice.
东西一点不吃 小费一分不少
She always tips on what she would have eaten.
大家伙儿注意了  我有个秘密
Guess what, everyone? I have a secret.
你其实是女人  只是误入男身吗?
You are a woman trapped in a man's body?
不是
No.
你其实是男人  误入了女身
You are a man trapped in a woman's body
其实你是个小男娃  却长了个小女娃的身体
You are a little boy trapped in a little girl's body.
我是一个入了男身的真男人好吧
I am a man in a man's body.
我们可不是在聊你的夜生活
We are not talking about your night life.
在浏览员工就职申请表时  我发现了一件事
I've discovered something when going over the employee applications.
好吧  虽然我永远不可能在Waldorf Astoria酒店工作
Okay. Perhaps I never worked at the Waldorf Astoria
但我确实在Astoria和一个叫Waldorf的共事过
but I did work with this guy, Waldorf, in Astoria.
和你没关系  我发现明天是Caroline的生日
It's not you. Tomorrow is Caroline's birthday.
为什么我不知道?  她明明啥都告诉我
Why wouldn't I know that? She tells me everything about her life.
我对她了如指掌
I know so much about her cycle,
要我生出她这样的女儿  真是巧妇难为啊
I'm feeling pressure to impregnate her.
我可以帮你哦
I can do that for you.
真是怪事  她怎么会不愿意让人帮她庆生呢
It's weird. Why wouldn't she want to celebrate her birthday?
什么事她都要庆祝一下
She celebrates everything.
注意啦  大家看过来
Heads up, everybody.
我刚刚把一次性毛巾装满了哦
I just refilled the paper towels.
最具团队精神的不二人选哟  哇哦
Who is a teamplayer? What, what!
破产姐妹   第一季    第十八集
天天美剧字幕组
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
=============================
听译:阿飘 大Z 安小姐
校对: T蓝 Raphael 逍⊙ 安东尼尼 安小姐 月球背面 水果虫虫 猴子
时间轴: 阿飘 猫小七 月球背面
=============================
Max
你该知道咱们要做什么了吧
You know what we have to do.
哎  我早知道会有这么一天
Oh, man. I knew this day would come.
说吧  我要怎样费点皮毛之力才能保住这份工作
All right. What's the least amount I can do to keep my job?
等你干完了通知我一声...
Just tell me when it's over...
...啥时候开始干也通知我一下
...and when it starts.
是时候谈谈怎么给Caroline庆生了
It's time to talk about Caroline's birthday.
你该给她办个生日聚会
You have to throw her a party.
刚刚用小男人的语气和我说不就得了
I'd rather you just have your tiny way with me.
我不喜欢过生日  我甚至都不知道自己
I don't like birthdays. I don't even know
是哪天生的
when mine is.
我妈妈估摸着  把范围缩小到6月的某两周中
My mom narrowed it down to a two-week-window in June.
你可是Caroline最好的朋友啊
But you are Caroline's BFF.
最好朋友就该为对方办生日
And it is BFF's job is to throw friend a party.
Han  我哪有钱来举办生日聚会啊
Han, I don't have enough money to throw a party.
我连扔棒球的钱都没有
I don't even have money to throw a baseball.
你有钱啊  你可以当她最好的朋友嘛
You have money. You be her BFF.
我已经有个铁哥们了  他叫JaMarcus
I already have a BFF. JaMarcus.
我上次生日  他为我筹划了场盛大的惊喜生日派对呢
And my last birthday, he threw me a sick surprise party.
你肯定以为最好朋友指的就是  "最多只能算损友"
You must think BFF stands for "Barely Freaking Friends".
你哪有可能认识叫JaMarcus的朋友
Because there is no way you are done with someone named JaMarcus.
哦  是吗?  那我们还铁到交换ATM取款的密码呢
Oh, really? Then why did we exchange ATM pin numbers.
把这个剪辑好  网站差不多就可以运营了
I just crop that, and we'll be good to go.
Max  Edwin正要展示我们新网站的设计呢
Max. Edwin is ready to show us the design for our new website.
去看看吧
Come see it.
姐们  你和那个网络高手已经谈了整整一周业务了
Dude, you and the webmaster have been talking business everyday for a week.
有什么进展吗?
Is something going on there?
咋样  网站现在怎么也该建得很高端了吧?
Shouldn't the web be mastered by now?
纯属业务往来
It's strictly business.
好吧  但我们可是付了200美元诶  总该尝点儿甜头吧
Alright. But it's costing us $200. Might as well get something out of it.
要不  让他"浏览"你性感小野猫的一面
Maybe let him browse your yahoo?
他似乎有个"大"容量"硬"盘驱动哦  运转迅"猛"
Looks like he might have a big ol' hard drive with a lot of ram.
他是挺帅
Yeah, he is cute.
但我现在不想和任何人谈恋爱
But I don't want a relationship right now.
也不想沾一夜情
And I don't do one-night stands.
好吧  那别"站"着了  快躺下呗
All right, so don't stand. Lay down.
在次日早上窘迫地走人可不是我的风格
That's not me, the next morning, doing the walk of shame.
我常看见那些一夜纵情后顶着一头乱发的女生
I always see those girls with their messed-up sex hair,
提着高跟鞋  拉紧外套好遮住昨夜激情时的工具
carrying their heels, clutching their coats to hide last night's outfit.
走进Kinko's   通过谷歌地图
Going in the Kinko's to use Google Maps,
才能弄明白自己在哪
so you can figure out where you are.
"Kinko"这点说得真是"神来之笔"
You really put the "ho" in "Kinko".
不好意思  Sophie  我们打烊了
Oh, sorry, Sophie, we are closed.
别嘛  我很快的  只拿个小蛋糕就走
Oh no, I'll be quick, I just want a cupcake to go.
我准备全天健康饮食呢
I'm on my way to 24-hour fitness.
我把它放在我跑步机上的小蛋糕支架上
And I put it in the cupcake holder on a treadmill.
对了  Max  我的车停在门口
Oh, Max, my town car is parked out front
想问下你  要不要等等你和Caroline
and I was wondering if you wanted me to wait for you and Caroline
我来载你们一起回家
to give you a ride back to our building.
没关系  别等了  我们还要打扫店面  把垃圾清出去
Oh no, it's okay. We still have to clean up and take the garbage out.
好
Oh.
哦哦  看来垃圾自己跳出来了
Ooh, looks like the garbage is taking itself out.
游戏继续
The game continues.
这是我的号码
Here is my number.
我邀请你给我打电话  可在意识到我是个性感尤物后打...
I invite you to call me when you realize what a catch I am...
...当然也可喝醉后愿意献身时
...or anytime you are drunk and willing.
Max  我要一个打包的袋子
Max, I'm going to need the doggy bag as well,
不是用来装小蛋糕的
yah, not for the cupcake,
是用来吐的
to puke in.
我会搞定最终设计  然后明天到餐馆来
So I'll get this fanalized and I'll stop by the diner tomorrow,
这样你就可在网站运营前确认版面设计
so you can sign off on the layout before we go live.
我好激动
This is so exciting.
等一下  Edwin  糟糕
Ooh, wait, Edwin. Shoot.
我忘记给你看新的价目表了
I forgot to show you the new pricing chart.
没关系  我现在就可以拟个草稿  然后回家的时候把它上传
It's cool. I can draft it up right now and upload it when I get home.
网络高手  你倒是挺快的嘛
Yeah, webmaster, you work pretty fast,
不过我肯定你也可以先慢慢做
but I bet you can work slow, too.
然后再来个加速冲刺
And really fast again.
我一分钟内就可以完事
I can be done in a minute.
呃  不是你想听到的吧
Ooh. Not what you wanna hear.
Max
没关系  我们可以等
It's fine. We can wait.
那啥?  你待在这儿吧  我先去趟商店
You know what? You stay here. I have to go to the store
- 为你的...拿点东西  - 我的什么?
- and pick up stuff for your... - My what?
为你的蛋糕生意拿点东西  是你硬拉着我一起做蛋糕生意的啦
Your cupcake business that you are making me do with you.
路上小心点
Get home safe!
呃...你住哪呀  Edwin?
Um...hey, where do you live, Edwin?
Hell's kitchen[位于纽约 与真人秀‘地狱厨房’同名]
Hell's kitchen.
挺好的
Oh, cool.
你要把"c"拿下来移到"l"那儿去吧
You're going to want to take the "c" down, transfer to the "l,"
要是你迷路了  在6道街和14道街就有Kinko's的门店哦
and if you get lost, there's a Kinko's on 6th and 14th.
让你见怪了  Max只是想...
That's embarrassing. Max was just trying to...
我懂  常和复杂的网络程序打交道
Yeah, I work on complicated web programs.
我想我已经破译她的密码了
I think I cracked that code.
她想让我俩约个会
She wants us to hook up.
是啊  抱歉了
Yeah, I'm sorry.
为什么说抱歉呢?
Why you are sorry?
我可是想了很久了
It's all I've been thinking about.
我的天呐
Oh my God.
他们打得真火热
They are so hot.
别这样看着姐
Don't give me that look.
Oleg
Caroline
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
那你在这干嘛?
我住这
I live here.
我刚刚才出去买了杯咖啡回来
And I’m just coming out from going to get coffee
那家咖啡超好喝的  我喝得一滴都没剩...
It was delicious I drank every bit of it...
在外面喝完了  所以没有杯子
outside. That’s why I don’t have a cup.
但你还穿着昨晚的衣服
But you’re wearing the same outfit from last night.
你不也穿着昨晚的那套
You are wearing the same out fit from last night.
你还顶着一头纵情一夜式发型
And you have messed-up sex hair.
你才是纵情一夜式发型呢
You have messed-up sex hair.
网络高手?
Webmaster?
Sophie?
她打电话给我  然后我们用手手爱爱了
She called me up and we made hand love.
但是我以为Sophie讨厌你
But I thought Sophie hated you.
但她不讨厌我的手
Well she doesn’t hate my hand.
你不能告诉其他人
But you cannot tell anyone.
这是她提出的一个条件
That was her one condition.
此外还要我提供了一份有职业医生签字的近期血样复本
That and a copy of my recent blood tests signed by medical professional.
成交  你也不能告诉别人我的事
Deal. And you can not tell anyone about me either.
尤其是Max  她会念叨死我的
Especially Max, I'd never hear the end of it.
成交
Deal.
拉勾?  还是  算了吧
Pinky swear?  Actually never mind
天知道你的手指摸过哪里
I don’t know where your fingers have been.
我才告诉你它们都摸过什么
I just told you where they’ve been.
Max
我为这个聚会激动了好一番
I’m so excited for this party.
还穿了我宽松的衣服来  打算跳一整夜舞
I wore my loose clothing so I can dance all night.
天啊  我实在扛不住举办聚会的压力了
God, I can’t take this party pressure.
我要到后面去  拿个开罐器割腕自杀
I'm just going to go in the back and run a can opener across my wrist.
Max  我相信你会做得很好
Oh Max, I’m sure you did a great job.
你知道只要有了DJ  有了香槟
you know as long as you have a DJ, some champagne,
再加上灵媒师就好
and a psychic.
没有  没有  就是没有  我买了些气球  一个鹰嘴豆拼盘
No no and no. I got some balloons, a hummus tray
还有Earl帮忙  他或许能拉个好朋友来撑场
and possibly Earl. He still has a good friend.
不用灵媒师  你都知道
You don’t need psychic to know
这会是个好可怕好可怕的聚会
that this is going to be a horrible horrible party.
感谢主 至少Caroline有个新调情男友
Well, thank God. Caroline has new boy toy
这样她就不会介意聚会有多烂了
she might not mind as much.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
我昨天看着他们在餐厅外面亲亲
Yeah, I saw them kissing in front of the diner last night.
没错  我坐在那  看了一个小时
Yeah, I sat there and watched for an hour.
他们真是干柴烈火啊
They are really going at it, hot and heavy.
就跟Showtime Network的直播一样  美好的旧时光
You know, like the Showtime Network in the good old days
哦  好极了   现在我还得请他?
Oh great. Now I have to invite him to the party, too?
我只有六盒Capri Sun  所以大家还要分着喝
I only got 6 pack of Capri Suns, so people are going to have to share.
隆重道贺
Congratulation, it’s official.
- 我们的网站上线了  - 隆重道贺
- Our website is now live. - Congratulation, it’s official.
你成了个荡妇
You are a whore.
我听说你的Kinko牌被捅了
I hear you got your Kinko's card punched.
什么
What?
别装傻  我知道你和那个网络高手滚过床单了
Don’t what me, I know you hooked up with the webmaster.
上菜
Pick up.
Oleg  你告诉Max了?
Oleg, you told Max?
发生什么事了?
What’s happening?
协议作废  Oleg昨晚和Sophie做爱了
Our deal is off. Oleg had sex with Sophie last night.
没...  不是做爱  只是手什么的  不...
No... It wasn’t sex. Just hand stuff. No...
而且没有到腰以上的地方  我可是个淑女
And noting above the waist. I’m a lady.
看到Caroline和大号Han亲热后  我欲火难耐
I got hot and bothered watching Caroline and big Han.
好吧
OK,
我真觉得这是我和Caroline的私事
you know I really think this is between Caroline and me.
你是说Caroline  你  还有脱衣舞女之间的事吧
You mean between Caroline, you and your strippers.
- 脱衣舞女?  - 我在脱衣舞俱乐部里见过这个男人
- Strippers? - I have seen this man in a strip club.
Han你去过脱衣舞俱乐部?
Han you were in a strip club?
Earl带我去的
Earl took me.
该死的  Han  你竟然出卖我
Damn it, Han. You're gonna sell me out
亏我还没说你把100破开  1美元1美元地赏那些小姐
after I spotted you a 100 dollars in ones.
你们去Spreader居然不叫我?
You went to Spreader without me?
你干嘛要带Han去脱衣舞俱乐部?
Why would you take Han to a strip club?
对啊  他的腿撑得住贴身舞么?
Yeah is his lap even big enough for dance?
Earl我对你很失望
Earl I’m so disappointed in you.
够了  我不参加你的聚会了
That’s it. I’m not going to your party.
什么聚会?
What party?
该死的  Earl  本来是要给她办生日惊喜派对的
Damm it Earl. That’s supposed to be the surprise for her birthday.
谁告诉你我生日的
Who told you it was my birthday.
Han
该死的 Han  我才不想要生日聚会
Damn it Han, I didn’t want a party,
我今年不想庆祝生日
I don’t want to celebrate my birthday this year.
好吧  太可惜了  你的最好朋友正准备给你个超大惊喜
Well too bad, your BFF is just throwing you a big blow-out.
Max  真的很遗憾
Oh Max, now I feel bad.
现在就感到遗憾了?  等着看你的聚会吧
Feel bad now? Wait till you see the party.
Caroline的生日  喔  喔
Caroline's birthday. Woot, woot.
谢谢  但你做的这一切早已胜过千言万语
Thanks, but you don’t have to say that after everything.
Max  我知道你的预算不多
Max I know you had limited budget,
可音乐不要钱啊
but music is free.
是啊  我就是个蠢货
Yeah well, I’m a douche.
发言
Speech!
这个聚会再开下去我可撑不住场了
I can’t carry this party much longer.
- 好吧 我想说点什么  - 等下 等下...
- OK I would like to say something. - Wait wait..
我们不能等到切蛋糕吗
Can’t we wait till we cut the cake.
蛋糕?
Cake?
世人如今还搞那玩意?
People are still doing that?
是的  我们的生计都靠它了
Yes, our livelihoods depends on it.
和现在一样差劲的聚会仅有一个
There’s only one party as bad as this one.
那就是当纳聚会
That’s the Donner party
起码他们吃得好
And even they had better food.
我想要道声生日快乐
I’d like to say happy birthday
把生日祝福送给这位我才欣然邂逅的漂亮女孩
to a pretty lady who I just had the pleasure of meeting
我希望以后能更多的了解她
and I think I’m gonna seeing a lot more of her.
- 我去拿点喝的  - 好的
- I’ll go get some more drinks. - Okay.
帮我甩了他
Get rid of him.
什么?
WHAT?
- 那不过是一夜贪欢  - 我以为你不是这种人
- It was one time thing. - I thought you were not that kind of girl.
我守身如玉将近一年  然后我意识到
I realize it’d been almost been a year since I had sex
没必要一直走以前的纯情路线
and I decided I rather not to be that kind of girl.
但是我又不想认真谈恋爱
But I don’t want a relationship.
嘿  我懂  撞了就跑啊
Hey  I get it. Hit it and quit it.
撞了就不要再回头
Hit it and don't babysit it ?
Max  拜托了
Max please.
好吧  要我怎么赶走他?
Fine.  How am I gonna make him go away?
从这个聚会赶人不需做任何思想工作
It’s not gonna take a lot to convince someone to leave this party
我原本想叫大家共举鸡尾酒杯祝酒的
I’d like to raise everyone to raise the cocktail
但是我没法子呀
but I can’t.
所以请对着太阳举起你的Capri果汁
So raise your Capri to the sun.
敬这位特别的女士  这位我愿意更多地去了解的女士
For the very special lady who I’m sure I will be seeing more of.
帮我甩了他  那不过是一夜贪欢
Get rid of him. It was a one time thing.
那么  这是你去过的最烂的聚会了?
So was that the worst party you’ve ever been to?
谁去过都会说它最烂
That was the worst party anyone has ever been to.
那个网络高手... 你们昨晚艳情可好?
So the webmaster. How was the sex?
相当好
Pretty good.
但是他有想要假装掐我的样子
But then he did that thing where he pretended he was going to choke me.
男人啥时开始好这一口了?
When did guys start doing that?
我不知道
I don't know,
不过我要早知道他好这口
but if I knew that was his thing,
我就叫他直接在聚会上掐死我得了
I would've asked him to choke me at the party.
你怎么帮我甩了他的?
How did you get rid of him?
你说了什么?  你有温婉地帮我拒绝他吗?
What did you say? Did you let him down gently?
不  我跟他讲该滚蛋了
No, I told him to hit the pike.
一夜情  是男生都懂
It's a one-night stand. Guys get that.
就这样?  他没闹情绪吗?
So that's it? He wasn't upset?.
男生才不在乎呢
Guys don't care.
一夜情的意思就是  他们高潮了  他们就该走了  字面上的意思
One-night stands-- they come, they go. Literally
但他要是又想和我约会怎么办?
But what if he wants to see me again?
别担心  他是不会跟恶鬼一样缠着你的
Relax. It is not going to come back to haunt you.
除非你开始觉得心痒难耐...
Unless you start feeling an itch...
或者感觉孩子在肚子里踢你
Or a kick.
好吧  谢谢你帮我甩了他  至于那个...
Well, thanks for dumping him. And for the...
我就直截了当说了吧  那个聚会
I'm going to go ahead and call it a party.
我知道你肯定不希望我动用小蛋糕基金
I knew you wouldn't want me to use any of the cupcake money,
况且我又一穷二白
and I was broke.
那我是你的BFF咯...
So I guess I am your BFF--
你永远的破产姐妹
your Broke Friend Forever.
Max  你做了什么真的没关系的
Max, it's really doesn't matter what you've done.
我之前对生日的唯一渴盼就是能在那天去看看我的父亲
The only thing I really wanted for my birthday was to see my father.
而他现在在监狱里  所以这个愿望无法实现
And he is in prison, so that didn't happen.
我可能不是个合格的最好朋友  可能也无力举办一场绝妙的聚会
I may not be a good BFF, I may not throw a great party,
但我确实知道怎么找到一辆免费的探监巴士啦
but I do know where to find a free bus to prison.
嘿  大家好  这闺女今天过生日哦
Hey everybody we got a birthday girl on board.
你给老子坐回去
Sit your ass back down.
看吧  巴士也欢乐
See now we‘ve got a party.
出城一趟  真是挺好的
This is nice, getting out of the city.
- 让我想起以前去汉普顿斯的旅程[Hamptons 美国度假胜地]  - 喂
- Kinda reminds me of the ride to the Hamptons.  - Yo.
第一次上这趟干线巴士么?
This your first on the bang bus?
我们叫它干线巴士  因为车上每个人
We call this a bang bus because everybody
都等着被干
here gonna get banged.
而且它又是一辆巴士
And in addition ‘cause we are on a bus.’
说得有理
Make sense.
- 嘿  我叫Shonda  - 我叫Max  这是Caroline
- Hey, I am shonda.  - I am Max, this is Caroline.
所以说你是去  那个  婚内探访的吗?
So you're all going for, like, conjugal visits?
和肖申克被拐到三腿小床上相比  婚内探访也差不多是这回事
Pretty fancy term for getting shawshanked on a three-leg cot.
肖申克吗?  我喜欢你这女孩
Shawshanked? I like her.
我喜欢你的头发  你才从坎昆回来吗?
I like your hair. Did you just get back from Cancun?
不  不  我很节省  从不旅游  我这头发是特意为我男人做的
No, no. I saved up, and I got these done for my got my man;
他说我这样很像Alicia Keys和"野兽良民"里的Ed Norton的华丽合体
he says they make me look like Alicia Keys meets Ed Norton in American History X
嘴真甜
How sweet
嘿  你男人是怎么进去的?
Yo, what’s your man in for?
我家男人进去是因为他有个诱人犯罪的性感屁屁
My man is in for possession of a sweet sweet ass
他这几句破话每次都要说一遍
He makes that joke every time.
我不是去看我男人  实际上我是去看我爸爸
He is not my man, actually he is my dad.
哦呦赫  你是个恋父癖咯
Oh so you are a freak!
没关系啊  我不乱评判人的
That’s alright I don’t judge.
你有看到我身上挂个名牌 写着Judy吗?
You saw a name tag on me that says Judy?
看  我们刚刚过Carvel了
Oh, look we just passed Carvel.
那是啥?
What’s a Carvel?
Carvel冰淇淋啊  就是那个鲜酱小鲸鱼  脆脆冰少女的那个
Carvel Ice-cream? You know the Fudgie the Whale, Cookie Puss?
搞没搞错啊  Carvel遍地都是  你怎么会不知道啊
Come on, how could you not know Carvel, they have them everywhere.
等下  就是穷酸白人大众吃的那种冰淇淋吗
O wait is that the white trash ice cream
你还敢说  它可不是穷酸白人才吃的
How dare you that is not white trash.
不是我盛气凌人啊  麻烦你睁开眼看看  是谁正坐在个免费的干线巴士上等着去监狱
And I wouldn’t be so high and mighty, you are in the free bang bus to the prison.
不好意思哦  我都不知道
I am sorry, I didn’t realize
你对冰淇淋还有这么深厚的感情啊
that you have such a strong emotional connection to the ice cream.
不是冰淇淋  是冰淇淋蛋糕
Not to the ice cream. The ice cream cake.
十岁的时候我求我妈给我办个生日聚会
When I was ten I ask my mom for a birthday party
她答应得好好的  结果嗑药嗑昏过去  完全忘了这茬
she said yes but then flaked out and forgot to call anyone.
我现在开始明白你为什么讨厌生日聚会了
Starting to understand why you don’t like birthday parties.
在门廊上干等了一个小时后  我偷了二十块钱
So after I waited on the porch for an hour I stole twenty bucks from a purse
拦了个便车直奔Carvel  给自己买了个鲜酱小鲸鱼
thumbed out to the Carvel and brought myself a Fudgie the Whale cake.
拿着把小粉塑料勺将它全吃了  什么样的聚会能比得上这个啊
Ate the whole thing with a pink plastic spoon and it was way better than any party ever gonna been.
听见了  鲜酱小鲸鱼  天下没得比
Heard that. And there ain’t nothing better than Fudgie the whale cake.
我喜欢上面那层巧克力碎酱
I love the chocolate crunchies.
奶奶的  是个人都喜欢那个白痴巧克力碎酱
Bitch everybody love the damn chocolate crunchies
你好  Shonda  来这儿见谁?
Hey Shonda who are you here to see?
谁现在有空?
Who’s available?
哎呀妈我尊是太搞笑了  你知道我来见我们家Squirm的嘛
I'm just cracking wise. You know I'm here to see Squirm.
给她搜身
Search her.
坑爹啊  又轮到我?
Damn it’s my turn again?
下一个
Next.
我们不在名单上面  没有提前预约
We’re not on that list, we didn’t call ahead.
看我的  姐姐这辈子就没有进不去的地方
Leave it to me. I’ve got into any club I have ever wanted to get into.
嘿  我是Caroline Channing  带个朋友
Hi, Caroline Channing, plus one.
名单上没有你
I don’t see you on the list.
真的?  那奇怪了  我们应该在上面的  我们一直都在名单上
Really? That’s weird we should be on the list, we’re always on the list.
Max  我们居然不在这个名单上诶
Max, we’re not on the list.
此话当真?  看我回去不把我那助理给宰了
We’re not? I am gonna kill my assistant.
哦  我明白了  我们的名字可能就列在Deangelo Jefferson下面呢
Oh I know, it might be under Deangelo Jefferson.
拜托  姑娘们  别浪费我时间了
Come on girls, don’t waste my time.
我要见你们经理
I’d like to see your manager.
我们这儿没有经理  这里是监狱啊
There is no manager. It’s a prison.
那这儿归谁管?
Well then who runs this place?
诶  Aryan兄弟会最近势头很猛  你要不要会会?
Well the Aryan brotherhood gets pretty strong.
他大概是新来的没眼力  给这门童五十块钱让他开开眼
This is such amateur hour, give me fifty bucks for the door guy.
你这是真要在监狱里  众目睽睽之下对政府人员行贿吗?
Are you seriously trying to bribe an officer of the law while inside of a prison?
你们触犯了联邦法律
That’s a federal offense.
真的?
Is it?
应该是吧
Probably.
从你提出收买时就该把你轰出去  我们从来不受贿
Look I should have you thrown out for even suggesting it, we do not except bribes.
好吧  这样  待会进去搜我身的时候  让你尝点甜头怎么样
Ok, fine. I will let you take your sweet time searching me on the way in.
这两个没问题  可以放进去
These two are clear the go through.
Max  我不能要你为我这么做
Max, you can’t do that for me.
这哪儿是为你  我也饥渴蛮久了  呜呼
It’s really for me, it’s been a while. Whoo-whoo.
这么久没见爸爸  好激动
So excited to see my father after all this time.
我看起来怎么样?
How do I look?
漂亮  我呢?  有没有青春无敌  光芒万丈?
You look good, how do I look? Do I still have that freshly felt-up glow?
那边那个红头发的肯定被你的光芒戳瞎眼了
Well that ginger over there thinks you look good,
他看你看得眼都直了
he’s full-on staring at you.
我也希望如此哈  要是沦落到连在监狱里憋死的男的都不看你
Well I should hope so. You can’t get a dude in prison to check you out;
那还不赶紧的去整容算了
it’s time for make over.
不是  他看着你直点头  好像认识你啊
No he’s looking and nodding, like he knows you.
我这辈子都没见过他好吧
Never seen him before in my life.
Max?  Max Black?
是我啊  Irish
It’s me, Irish.
我不认识你  兄弟  我看你是认错人了
I don’t know dude, I think you got the wrong girl.
Max  我怎么可能忘掉你的面容
Max I could never forget that face.
相信我  你从来都没见过我的
Trust me you’ve never seen me before.
- 我的妈  - 天哪
- Oh damn!  - Oh my god.
他肚子上是你
That’s you!
看  你记得的
See you do remember.
当然了
Of course.
帮我甩掉他  那只是一夜情
Get rid of him. It’s a one night stand.
跟你说了吧  一夜风流债追上门了
See they do come back and haunt you.
穿上衣服
Shirt on!
Max  你能相信吗  世界上有这么多监狱
Max can you believe it, of all the prisons in all the world
你却偏偏走进这一间
you’ walked into mine.
命运在咆哮啊
It’s kismet.
我帮你甩过人一回了  这回你替我上
I get rid of yours, you get rid of mine.
听着  Irish  你们之间就不过是一夜风流
Listen Irish, it was a one time thing,
你是个男人  你懂的
you’re a guy you get that.
你不能说什么一夜风流的话啊  我爱你的!
You can’t just say it’s a one time thing, I love you!
我当时还替你吹墨西哥菜泡饭来着
I blew up that chipotle for you.
听着  你的纹身我很震撼  但是我根本不相信爱情  而且说实话
Listen I appreciate the ink but I don’t really believe in love and truth be told ,
我根本就不喜欢墨西哥菜
I am not even a fan of Mexican food.
Caroline Channing来了吗?  这桌子等着
Caroline Channing?  This table.
Max快点  我爸爸马上来了
Max we have to go, my dad is coming.
见到你很高兴  你这样子  看的我激动得想吐
Nice to see you Irish, your body looks sick!
- Max等等  - 你小心点  给我往后站
- Max, hold on.   - I am not gonna tell you again to back up.
Max  我不要再次失去你
Max, I am not gonna lose you twice.
- 我说往后站  - 这是我一生的挚爱  你叫我怎么往后站
- I said back up!  - Don’t tell me to back up, that’s a love of my life.
拜托  大哥  滚蛋吧
Come on dude, hit the pike.
- 冷静点  - 冷静你妹啊
- Clam down  - Don’t tell me to calm down.
探视时间到此为止  大家速速离开
Visiting hours are over, everybody out!
不行  等等  我不能走
Wait wait, I can’t leave.
等等  我爸爸在那儿
No wait there’s my father!
我看见他了  他马上就出来了  爸爸
I can see him, he is just coming in. Daddy!
爸爸  嗨
Daddy hi!
两位大侠  拜您所赐
Well, thank you every much ladies.
我被拉出来的时候  我男人还没进去呢
My man was barely in when I got pulled out.
我对不起你们
I would like to apologize to everyone
大家白坐了一趟干线却没有干成
for taking the bang out of the bus.
但不是我为自己开脱  咱们这儿有谁没有被脑残分子坑过的
But in my own defense everyone here knows a little something about crazy guys.
你给老子坐回去
Sit your ass back down,
坐下来吧  不然又要天下大乱了
Sit down before you start another riot.
对不起这次又弄砸了  你好不容易能见你爸爸一面  给我搅合了
I am sorry I blew it. I screwed up your chance to see your father,
你的生日聚会也给我办砸了
I screwed up your party,
就连买个蛋糕给你过生日这样最简单的事  我都没办好
I’ve screwed up the easiest birthday thing to do, like to get a cake.
我是天字第一烂的朋友
I am a terrible BFF.
没事的  真的  我不介意
It’s ok. Really it’s fine.
这一年过的这么烂  也不是说你给我买个蛋糕  就什么问题都解决了
With the year I am having it’s not like you could have made everything better by just getting me a cake.
哦  当然不是随便什么蛋糕了
Oh no, not just any cake.
一如既往的好吃啊
Just as good as I remember it.
我们这辈子就这40美金花得最值
Best 40 bucks we’ve ever spent.
而且这个生日过的  也不是很烂嘛
And this birthday turned out to be alright.
我想要的都得到了   还见了爸爸一面
I did get what I wanted and I got to see my father.
虽然只是昙花一现  但毕竟我看到了他
It was only for a second but I saw him,
他也看到了我  谢谢你
and he saw me. So thank you.
是啊  我也见到了Irish
Yeah and I got to see Irish.
我本以为他是从我生命中溜走的那个人
Think he might be the one that got away.
好吧  是被架走的那个人
Well, the one that got put away.
我觉得你和我好过BFFs
You know you and I are better than BFFs.
我们是BBFs  干线巴士朋友
We’re BBFs. Bang Bus Friends.
欢迎加入天天美剧字幕组
www.ttmeiju.com
@天天美剧
[Waldorf Astoria酒店  著名豪华酒店]
[同名的JaMarcus Russell是一个身高2米多的四分卫]
[Kinko's: 一家以印务为主的全球连锁公司  后被联邦快递收购]
[cool变成oolc  即On One night Love Caroline: 一夜柔情Caroline]
[Showtime Network  尺度开放的台]
[Capri Sun 可口可乐公司旗下某浓缩果汁牌子]
[注: 当纳聚会的成员们在1846年试图抄近道去加利福尼亚的故事  美国史上人吃人传说]
[出自电影"肖申克的救赎"主人公肖申克曾在监狱里被猥亵]
[Cancun: 坎昆  墨西哥著名旅游城市  在加勒比海岸]
[Alicia Keys: 著名女歌手  Ed Norton: 著名男演员  在American History X"野兽良民"里增肥三十磅出演白人至上的暴徒]
[Judge Judy（直译为"评判员Judy"）是美国一档电视节目]
[Carvel: 一家出售手工冰激凌软蛋糕的连锁店  产品多为应节应景的卡通形象  分别代表一个节日]
[均为Carvel的招牌卡通型冰淇淋软蛋糕  常常分别作为父亲节和母亲节的礼物]
[The one that got away是歌手Katy Perry的大热单曲]
[暗指Han不太可能交到JaMarcus这样的猛男]